Congratulations! You've made it to the end of this course on ES6.
تهانينا! لقد وصلتم إلى نهاية هذه الدورة ES6.
You mean ES2015, right? Sure, whatever.
أنت تقصد ES6، أليس كذلك؟ بالتأكيد، مهما كان.
Look, you've made it to the end of this course on the future of JavaScript.
انظروا، لقد وصلتم إلى نهاية هذه الدورة المتعلقة بمستقبل لغة JavaScript.
Before you go, let's not forget about the things you've learned during this course.
قبل أن تذهبوا، دعونا لا ننسى الأشياء التي تعلمتموها أثناء هذه الدورة.
In lesson one, you learned about
في الدرس الأول، لقد درستم
the most recent syntax additions to the JavaScript language.
أحدث إضافات في بناء الجملة إلى لغة JavaScript.
In lesson two, you discovered
في الدرس الثاني، لقد تعرفتم على
new ways for writing functions and how to create JavaScript classes.
طرق جديدة لكتابة الدوال وطريقة إنشاء فئات JavaScript.
In lesson three, you were exposed to the latest built-ins provided to you in ES6.
في الدرس الثالث، تعرفنا على أحدث الخصائص المضمنة المقدمة لكم في ES6.
And, in lesson four,
وفي الدرس الرابع،
we wrapped it up by showing you how to incorporate ES6 into your next JavaScript project.
لقد أنهيناه بتوضيح طريقة استخدام ES6 في مشروع JavaScript التالي.
We hope you found this course to be insightful and it will inspire
نأمل أن تكون هذه الدورة مفيدة لكم ويكون مصدر إلهام لكم
you to start using ES6 in whatever projects you work on in the future.
لبدء استخدام ES6 في جميع المشروعات المستقبلية لديكم.